<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rodders</title>
    <link>https://rodders.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rodders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:15:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rodders.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Food Standards Agency Alerts Analysis</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/projects/fsa-safety-alerts/fsa-safety-alerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/projects/fsa-safety-alerts/fsa-safety-alerts/</guid>
      <description>Analysis of Food Standards Agency Alerts Link to heading Report Index Link to heading Report Introduction Summary Pathogenic Contaminants Allergenic Contaminants Foreign Material Contaminants Other Contaminants / Issues Contaminants by Product Type Analysts Notes Link to heading Meta Data Feature Engineering Abstract Link to heading This report presents a comprehensive review of the food safety alerts issued by the UK Food Standards Agency. The analysis provides insights into the frequency, types, and relevant information about each alert, covering an eight year period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Mainstream Media -  Investigating Mainstream Media Sentiment towards Electric Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/projects/ev-headlines/project-uk-mainstream-media-ev-bias/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 09:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/projects/ev-headlines/project-uk-mainstream-media-ev-bias/</guid>
      <description>Analysis of bias in headlines against Electric Vehicles by UK Mainstream Media Link to heading Abstract Link to heading This study analysed the sentiment of mainstream media headlines towards electric vehicles (EVs) from August to January, capturing a dataset of 1,976,938 datapoints across ten prominent UK publications, including
The Sun The Express The Times The Telegraph Daily Mail Economist The BBC The Independent The Spectator The Daily Star Notably, The Telegraph, The Spectator, The Independent, and the Daily Mail were responsible for over 73% of all EV-related headlines, highlighting their disproportionate influence on public discourse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU SafetyGate Report 2023</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/projects/eu-safety-gate/project-eu-safety-gate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 09:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/projects/eu-safety-gate/project-eu-safety-gate/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated Latest Week 26/08/2024 week 34 The EU Safety Gate project Link to heading About this Project Link to heading I first encountered the EU Safety Gate in my previous role.
Since 2003, the Safety Gate has enabled a quick exchange of information among EU/EEA Member States and the European Commission about dangerous non-food products posing a risk to the health and safety of consumers. Appropriate follow-up has to be taken by the national authorities so that the notified dangerous products are removed from the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salifort Motors - Google Advanced Analytics Capstone Project</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/projects/salifort_project/salifort-motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/projects/salifort_project/salifort-motors/</guid>
      <description>Google Advanced Data Analytics Capstone Project - Salifort Motors Link to heading Overview Link to heading Salifort Motors (The Client) is a fictitious company experiencing significant loss of employees. They have created a project team to provide data driven suggestions for the HR team to implement to improve employee retention.
The estimated cost of lost employees to the client is in the order of £42m for 2022, for 1,991 employees who left employment in 2022, representing 20% of all employees (10,000).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMMT - UK Electric Vehicle Registrations (and other fuels)</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/projects/smmt-google-analytics-project/uk-vehicle-registration-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 09:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/projects/smmt-google-analytics-project/uk-vehicle-registration-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Project Goal Link to heading To obtain additional monthly car registration data to add to my DVLA Registration Dashboard in Tableau.
Monthly Vehicle Registration by Fuel Type and Keepership Link to heading This is additional data being added to the DVLA Registered Vehicles dashboard I maintain on Tableau. The DVLA data is issued annually and only gives annual totals for registered vehicles. SMMT publish data monthly in an image format and this project, grabs that data from the images and processes it into a CSV file suitable for import into Tableau.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google ADVANCED Data Analytics Course Passed!</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/posts/2023-10-26-google-advanced-data-analytics-completed-/google-advanced-data-analytics-completed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/posts/2023-10-26-google-advanced-data-analytics-completed-/google-advanced-data-analytics-completed/</guid>
      <description>https://coursera.org/share/06a6ec416a2c8bddbdea6858dbf0c5d4
Google&amp;rsquo;s Advanced Data Analytics Course Link to heading I have successfully completed and passed Google&amp;rsquo;s Advanced Data Analytics Course!
The course covered a wide array of topics, from advanced data processing techniques and complex analytical methods to visualizing and presenting data in compelling ways. Each module was designed to build not just theoretical knowledge but practical skills that I could immediately apply. Through hands-on projects and case studies, I delved deep into the nuances of BigQuery, data visualization, and machine learning, gaining insights that have already begun to transform the way I approach data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DVLA Data - Google Data Analytics Portfolio Project</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/projects/dvla-data-google-analytics/google-data-analytics-portfolio-project-dvla-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/projects/dvla-data-google-analytics/google-data-analytics-portfolio-project-dvla-data/</guid>
      <description>Course Portfolio Project Link to heading For the completion stage of the Google Data Analytics Specialisation course we were asked to complete a data analysis project from start to finish. This allowed me to apply much of the lessons learned during the course to something I had some passion about: sustainable energy and transportation. Specifically looking at the adoption of Electric Vehicles in the UK, which in turn led me on to the broader issues of media messaging around this topic, which has become a separate topic, the bot is running as you read this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Analytics Course Passed!</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/posts/2023-08-14-google-data-analytics-completed/google-data-analytics-completed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/posts/2023-08-14-google-data-analytics-completed/google-data-analytics-completed/</guid>
      <description>https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/professional-cert/L4GS97QJ8KCZ
A Milestone Achieved Link to heading Completing the Google Data Analytics Specialization on Coursera 📊
A few months ago, I was unfortunately made redundant which gave me the opportunity to reflect and decide what I really wanted to do when I grew up. This little voyage of discovery led me to the world of data analytics and data science and I decided to re-enter education and develop some new skills in these fast growing and changing specialisations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/contact/</guid>
      <description>How can I help you? Link to heading Get in contact, lets have a chat
rod.slateruk@gmail.com
https://github.com/rodders99
https://rodders.me
https://www.linkedin.com/in/rod-slater-uk/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unofficial Chronicles of Me</title>
      <link>https://rodders.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodders.me/about/</guid>
      <description>An Introduction to Yours Truly Link to heading Imagine a world where floppy disks were the ultimate symbol of technological advancement, and the sound of a modem connecting was the sweetest symphony. That was my playground. At the tender age of 12, courtesy of a dad who believed in living on the tech edge, a Tandy TRS-80 made its grand entrance into our home. It was followed by a Commodore Pet (because why settle for cassette tape when you can have two floppy disk drives?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
